

Full Stack Developer | Team Leader



ABOUT ME

Managing to become an experienced full stack developer, durring my career I have been acumulating a lot of experience, being involved in many projects and many types of environments. As a software enginner I consider myself a very organized and strict guy when it comes up to code quality. I like to teach, I like to do classes with others and to share every experience I've been lucky to learn from. Excepting programming, my second passion is to compose electronic music, of course, on a computer.



EDUCATION

Babes Bolyai University,
Computer Science Department (2013-2016)

Avram lancu Highschool Intensive Informatics

(2009-2013)



EXPERIENCE



(2018-2018)

Uniqa Raiffeisen Software Solutions

(2016-2018)

ServusTech

(2015-2016)

Ambo Software

(2014-2015) Retfair

Full Stack Developer & Team Leader

Outsourcing industry

Java Contractor

Self Product, Banking and Insurrance industries

Full Stack Developer

Outsourcing industry

Java Developer

Outsourcing industry

Automation QA & Performance Tester

Self product, gambling industry



LANGUAGES

Romanian

English

German



HOBBIES

- Music Production
- Snowboarding
- Reading
- Cars & Motorcycles
- Playing piano



SKILLS

Java 8
Spring
Microservices
SQL/JDBC
Big Data
Async
Hibernate
Maven
REST
SOAP

Angular
JavaScript
HTML
CSS
UX Design
Kafka
TestNG
AWS
WebSockets

EJB